An app marketplace is where customers can
discover and buy mobile apps and games.
The Google Play store and
the Amazon Appstore are two examples
of Android app marketplaces.
In this course,
you're learning how to build apps, so it's
likely that you'll also want to make some
of those apps available to the public.
In this lesson from our
colleagues at Amazon,
you'll learn how to register as
a developer for an app marketplace and
how to submit your Android app to that
marketplace so that it's available for
download to millions of potential
customers around the world.
This lesson will show you how to
create a developer account and
then how to submit an app
to the Amazon Appstore.
And we're focusing on the Amazon Appstore
because registration is free.
But, of course, once you've seen
how the Amazon Appstore works,
you should also have a general idea of how
the Google Play store works should you
decide to get an account there as well.
Now, to submit an app to
the Amazon Appstore, the first step is to
register for a developer account
with the Amazon Appstore.
And to do that, please go to this link for
step-by-step instructions on how to
create a developer account
in less than ten minutes.
As I mentioned in an earlier video,
Amazon is also sponsoring an ebook,
Creating Mobile Apps with HTML,
for all students in this course.
And this should help you in understanding
some of the tradeoffs between
developing native Android apps like
we've been doing in this course and
developing web-based apps that run
in a browser on your mobile device.
Additionally, all students
will also get free access to
an HTML5 Mobile Game Development
by Example online tutorial.
And to receive your benefits,
first register as a developer
with the Amazon Appstore.
Then, go to this link and
submit your information,
including your developer account name.
Instructions and
discount codes on how to get free
access to the ebook and the online
tutorial will be delivered to you within
two weeks of submitting the survey.
Thank you.